Wow! It's Pororo!
Hi, Pororo
Hello friends
Hello my good friends
Let's play together
with playful Pororo
Hello friends
Hello my good friends
Let's jump together
PorongPorongPororo
PorongPorongPororororo
Always having fun with playful
Little Penguin Pororo
Sweet and cute my playful friend
PorongPorong
PorongPorongPororo
Ready or not, here l come
Playing hide and seek
Merrier together
playing with lots of friends
Rock! Scissors! Paper!
Even when playing tag
Happier together
playing with Pororo
PorongPorongPororororo
Always having fun with playful
Little Penguin Pororo
Sweet and cute
my playful friend
PorongPorong
PorongPorongPororo
It's morning
Where are Loopy and Petty
going in such a hurry?
Poby
Who is it?
Poby, Harry
Don't get up so fast!
I'm sorry, Harry
Poby, Harry
Huh?
Hi
What are you doing here
so early?
Hello.. Sleepy heads
Did you forget what day it was?
What day is it?
It's the day that
Pororo and Crong are flying
That's right
You guys! Hi
Huh?
Hi
CrongCrong
Where's your plane?
Here we go
Huh?
Hello! You're all here
Eddy, is this the plane?
Yes..Why?
This is going to fly?
Yes, it is
I made it specially for Crong
CrongCrong
Are you ready?
Yes!
CrongCrong
Off you go!
Wow
Crong!
Uhh..
Oh no!
Pororo's plane crashed!
Huh?
Don't be disappointed
in case of something like this
I made a more powerful plane
Tahtah!
Wow
Crong,Crong
Wow..This is fantastic
CrongCrong
Will it work?
Well..
Are you ready?
Take off!
Yes!
CrongCrong
Huh?
This time they crashed
in to a mountain
This time I'm sure it'll work!
You won't crash in to anything
like this..
Let's take off
CrongCrongCrong
Crong!Crong!
Pororo, your plane
is flying to outer space
Huh?
Popopo?
Pipipi?
Huh? What is that?
Hey! Look over there!
It's an U.F.O.!
We're back
CrongCrong
Pororo, Crong
Huh?
You're safe.. Huh?
CrongCrong
Popo?Pipi?
Who, who are they?
Oh,say hello
This is Popo
Popo
And this is Pipi
Pipi
They're friends I met
outer space
They are?
Hmm..
They look a bit different
Pi..
But.. their plane broke
because it crashed in to ours
Pipipi..Pipipi..
Popo, Pipi
It's getting late
Let's go over to my house
I'll make you something to eat
Pipipipi?
Popopo?
Now.. All done
Here you go
Popo?
Pipi?
Pipipi?
Like this..
Huh?
Popopo..Pipipi..Popop
Popo and Pipi
like the cookies, too
Look, I think they like it
Oh?
Popopo..
Pipipi..Pipipi..
have some more
Pororo and friends, and Popo
and Pipi became friends instantly
Hope they all become
good friends
I told you not to move!
Huh?Hmmm...
I can't draw
if you keep moving
Okay..
Kind of tough hanging there
huh, Poby?
Huh? Yes..
I'll sing a song for you
so hang in there
A song?
I'm, I'm, I'm
a little singing bird
I like to sing songs
for my friends
Lallala
You guys
Huh?
Here you are
CrongCrong
Poby, what are you doing?
I was singing a song for Poby
Since you're all here
I'll sing a new song for you
Harry
There're some cookies
that I made
Would you like some?
That sounds good
Let's go
Cookies?
CrongCrong?
CrongCrongCrong
What are you doing?
Huh? Cr,Crong!
You've ruined the painting!
Crong?
Hey, guys!
Here's the cookie!
Loo,Loopy!
Why don't we play tag
instead of eating cookie!
Tag? Then, let me finish
the painting and..
No.. Leave this here..
and let's go out
Huh? O,okay..
Here, here.. This way..
Crong, you too
CrongCrong
Tag? Let's go
Poby, come on out
What a relief
I'm coming
Who's going to be it?
Wait for me
I wonder
what Popo and Pipi are doing?
Popopo..I. Think. It's. Done
Let's. Try. It. Then
Popopo
Po? Popo?
Pipipi!
Let. Me. Try. It!
Pipipi..
Popo?
Pipipi!
Pipi?
Pipipipi..
Pipipi..
Pipi?
it seems like Popo is hungry
Pipi! Loppy?
Now, all done!
Oh, Loopy made food
for them before
Popo and Pipi flew
over to Loopy's house
Where did every one hide?
Hmm..Huh?
Oops!
There he is
Loopy
Pipi?
No. Body. Is. Home
Popopo
Cookies!
Popo
Pipi
Po..Good..Po?
What..Is..This?
Popopo
Pipi
Pipi! Pipi? Pipipi!
Pipi. I'm. Sorry. Po?
Pipi..Pipipi..
Popopo!
Pipipi..pi!
Pipi..Stop..It..
Pipi!
Popo!
Pipipipi
Pipi..Stop..It..
Pipi!
Popo?
Pipipi Pipipi!
Pipi!
Pipipipi
Pipi, I'm..Sorry
Pipipi..
Pipipipipi..
Popopo!
Pi.. Pi.. Pi..
Popopopo..
Pipipi!
You guys
When did you come?
There.. Done
Thank. You..
Poppop
Pipipipi..
You..
Will clean this, won't you?
The house became a mess
because of Popo and Pipi
Popo, Pipi, we'll help
CrongCrong
Popo Popopo..
Pipi? What. Is. This?
Pipi!
Oh, It's cold!
Pipi?
Popo
That's a sprayer
You can spray water..
Oh!
Pipipipipi
Popo and Pipi
really like playing jokes
It's lateat night
But there're still lights on
at Eddy's house
Finished!
Eddy made a robot!
Now, let's see if it works
Now, if I wait a little while..
Hmm..
What's so noisy..
it became morning
Eddy
CrongCrong
Huh?
Hi
What are you doing here
so early in the morning?
You said that you'll show us
your new invention
Let's go in and see
Wow
CrongCrong
Wow..
This seems like the one
Now, let me turn it on
Like this and..
Hello..
My name is Rody
Wow.. It's moving
Hello, Eddy
Hello, Rody
Wow.. it talks..
Talk? Rody can do
more than that
Rody, show them
Show them?
Alright..I'll show you..
Oh..
Let's see..
Oh, yeah
Here I go! Fly!
Wow..
Uh?
Oops!
Rody, you can't fly
That's right..
I hope I can crawl
I can dance like this
Can you fix this then?
Let me see that
Umm..
Looks interesting..
What!
That's a camera
Rody, are you sure you can fix it?
Camera?
It's used to take pictures
Let's see..
Huh? It's not coming off..
Huh?
My camera broke!
Huh? Wait a minute..
Huh?
It's completely broken..
I, I'll fix this for you
Is there anything
that Rody can do well?
CrongCrong..
Someting I can do well?
That's..Eddy, what can I do?
Umm..
That's right.. He's strong..
Strong? I'm strong!
Strong?
See? I can lift more
I can lift more
Huh?
More, more, and more..
Dangerous!
Danger?
Oh..It's dangerous..
I think It's better to go out side
You guys
Over here!
Huh? Wow..
I made this
Wow.. You made it so big?
It's really big..
Crong..Crong
See?
I told you that Rody is strong
I can make a larger one
Wow..
I can push harder..
Watch out, Rody!
Huh?
Oh!
Let's show them something else..
Someting else?
Wait!
I better get going..
Me too..
It became night
Uh.. Rody..
Yes, Eddy
Come on sleep with me..
In the bed? Wow..
Yeah! Exciting!
Rody, I can't sleep with you..
Can't sleep with me?
Then..
I'll make a house for you instead
My house?
Yes
Wow
Thanks, Eddy
You're welcome
Many things happened today
But Eddy loves
his new friend Rody
Wow.. it looks fantastic
Eddy, is this really my house?
Yes, I told you that
I'll make you one
Wow.. It's my house
Wow..
Eddy made a house for Rody
Wow..Huh?
A bed?
Wow
Ohh.. This is fun
Rody, becareful
I'm alright.. Wow!
Oh..
I told you to becareful
I should be more careful..
Rody
Huh?
Hi
Hello, Friends
Congratulations
on your new home
Here's a present for you
I brought a book
I brought this for you
A mini car
CrongCrong
Ball..
Here, it's.. a bowtie
Wow.. Thanks
I can't see Loopy around
You're right
I'm over here
I brought some food to celebrate!
Wow..
Congratulations..
Now blow out the candle
The candle?
Rody..
Blow 'whoo' like this
and blow out the candle..
With my mouth?
You can't blow wind
from your mouth
Rody couldn't blow
out the candle
Now, shall we start eating?
Let's..
Tastes good
Rody
You can't eat food
I can't eat?
But Rody wanted to eat
just like his friends
Huh?
Rody tried to drink his milk
but he couldn't drink it
Tastes good.. Huh?
Oh, Rody spilled milk on his face
I love to play all day
Come join me all my friends
Someting is wrong with Rody
Rody, you're not supposed
to drink
Huh? He is waking up..
Rody, are you alright?
What a nice sleep
Thank, goodness!
Huh?
You can't drink
You'll break if you do
Don't eat anything from now on
Alright?
Huh?
We'll be going now
CrongCrong
Goodbye
Every one went home
in the evening
I'll be going home too
Bye
Rody was happy to have
a place of his own
The mini car
Let's try it
Huh?
Hmm.. Let's see
This is fun
Fun!
Huh?
it's.. Rody's voice..
What's.. Oh!
Huh?
Eddy, are you alright?
Rody, yes..
I'm alright
I'm sorry
It's alright
You didn't do it on purpose
Congratulations again, Rody
Eddy.. Thanks
O, okay
Let's go to sleep now
Okay
Rody was really happy
to have a friend like Eddy
CrongCrong
Crorong
Crong
Wow..It's a toy plane
CrongCrongCrong
Crong
Huh?
CrongCrong
Want to change?
CrongCrongCrong
Crong wanted to play
with the toy plane
No thanks
CrongCrong
Crong!
CrongCrongCrong..
Pororo
Huh?
Crong..Crong
You want me to roll the car?
Crong!
Do it yourself
Crong!CrongCrong!
Crong..Crong?
Crong..
CrongCrongCrongCrong..
Not so fast
Crong Corng!
Crong!
Humph!
Crong! Crong!
Crong Crong?
Crong Crong
Crong!
That's my car
Get off of it
Crong Nah!
Crong Crong
Stop right there!
Crong Crong..
Stop!
Crong..
Crong, you..
Get it
Crorong
Crong Crong
Huh? You!
Crong took the toy plane
and ran outside
Crong Crong
Crong
Crong Crong?
Popo and Pipi came by..
What. Are. You. Doing?
Crong!
Hide and seek! Crong Crong
Whide. And. Deek?
Oh.. Hide! And! Seek!
Huh?
Found you!
Crong!
Stop right there!
Let's go
Stop!
Crong Crong
Crong
Here you are
Crong left the toy plane
and ran away
Pororo Crong.. Huh?
Huh?
No one here
Hmm.. Huh?
Hmm.. it's.. a toy plane
Crong..Crong Crong!
Crong!
Stop right there!
Crong
Crong?
You, stop right there!
Crong Crong..
Got you!
Give me back the plane
Crong..
Huh?
Where did the plane go?
You guys
Hello
Huh?
Look, I found it
Huh? That's mine..
Huh?
It's yours? Oh.. Here
Glad I found it
Crong Crong
Huh?
Rody also wanted to play
with the toy plane
Here, Rody
Huh?
You can play with It..
Really? Thanks, Pororo
And.. Crong can play with it after
Crong?
I'm sorry about what I did
Let's share our toys
from now on
Crong Crong Crong
Pororo is so kind
It's more fun when you share
your toys with your friends
Pororo is going to ride
a plane again today
Everyone is here to see it
I'll be back
CrongCrong
Pororo, are you sure about this?
Don't worry
It's going to fly this time
CrongCrong
Wow.. It's flying
See? I told you it'll fly
CrongCrong
Yeah.. We're really flying
Be careful, Pororo
Don't worry
Wow
Wow.. Nice
Crong Crong
Huh?
What is that?
Alright
Let's go and see
in the deep, deep forest
There lived Tongtong the dragon
Cock a doodle doo
So it was this
Appear chicken..
Let's see
A little chick appeared
instead of a chicken
Huh? Weird
One more time..
Kuri kuri Tongtong
Appear chicken
Huh?
Oh! Kuri kuri Tongtong
Kuri kuri Tongtong disappear..
I should have an apple
instead of chicken..
This looks like the right place
Kuri kuri Tongtong
Appear apple..
There.. Huh?
Crong?
Huh?
An apple?
Crong
Huh? That's my apple..
Taking my apple..
That does it
I can't catch the plane
like this, can I?
Kuri kuri Tongtong
Kuri kuri Tongtong.. Change!
Huh? Thant's not It..
Ah, that's right
Kuri kuri Tongtong
Kuri kuri Tongtong Change!
Done
Yap! Yap!
How's that, Neat, huh?
Now, shall I go?
Huh?
Where did they go so fast?
Why aren't Pororo and Crong
coming back?
Wait, this sound..?
Oh..! It's plane!
Huh? It's our house
CrongCrong
Wow.. It's Pororo
Crong Crong
Hmm.. Huh?
Oh, Found them
Pororo, I'm glad you came back safe
Huh?
What is that?
Oh..
Here you are
Hi.. I'm glad to meet you all
But..
Wait!
Don't bother my friends!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
I'm the brave warrior Rody!
Here I go
What are you doing?
Well, I was.. that Is..
Let. Go. Of. My. Friend!
Let go? Okay..
Huh?
Pipipipi..
Who are you..
W, wait..
Huh?
Pipipipi..
What a sneeze.. Sorry
Are you alright?
My name is Tongtong
Oh, and this is
how I really look..
I've come to get my apple
Apple?
Crong?
Yes.. That apple is mine..
CrongCrong
Sorry
We didn't know that it was yours
That's alright
I'm sorry I startled you
I'll be going now..
Tongtong..
Since you've came all the way here
why don't you play with us?
is it alright?
Yes!
Then are we going to be friends?
Wow.. That's neat!
Tongtong was glad to have
made new friends
And our friends
were glad as well
But Tongtong will have
to be careful when he sneezes
Tongtong is showing magic
to his friends
What kind of magic is it?
Kurikuri Tongtong
Kurikuri Tongtong.. Change!
Huh?
The cactus turned
into a snow globe
Wow..
Tongtong, can you turn this
into a clock?
A clock? Hmm.. Okay
Kurikuri Tongtong
Kurikuri Tongtong.. Change!
Huh? It's the same
Huh?
What?
You, you changed into a clock
Oh..
What are you.. Huh?
Kurikuri Tongtong
Kurikuri Tongtong.. Change!
Wow
It's a rolling doll this time
Hmm..
Can't stay like this
Kurikuri Tongtong
Kurikuri Tongtong.. Change!
I should be going home now
Huh? Yeah..
There
Let's go.. Ouch!
Good bye
OK
Tongtong went back to his house
Huh? Harry!
Where's Harry?
Harry?
Harry has disappeared
What happened?
I'm home
I sometimes make mistakes
You already made
a mistake a while ago
Huh?
Hello
You want to learn magic?
Yes
But magic isn't something
you can learn
Why not?
Only a dragon can use my magic
Aha! Then can you make me
strong using magic?
Let's see..
Yes, It's here
Kurikuri Tongtong
Kurikuri Tongtong.. Change
Huh? It's the same
Try lifting the crystal ball
This? Let's see..
Oh.. Wow
Harry really did get stronger
Now you're the strongest bird
in the world..
I am? Good
But you must be careful..
Thanks, Tongtong Bye
I have to warn you..
Yeah
So I'm the strongest bird
in the world now.. Huh?
Already there..
Get one in..
Poby
Huh?
Harry! Where have you been?
I didn't see you a while ago..
A while ago?
Let me help you with that
Thanks, but you can't even lift
this hammer
Wrong.. This is nothing
Huh?
Here goes
Oh no
The door is broken
Um.. Was I too strong?
I think you're better
at it than I am
Oh..
Playing ball
Let me play too
It's you, Harry
But you can't even kick the ball..
You think?
Let me show you..
Huh? Was I too strong?
I should be going now
Oh..
Hm.. Huh?
The seesaw is not moving
No
Hello
Huh?
Let me ride it too
Glad you're here
You can sit on our side
Yes, over here
Thanks
Huh?
Harry won't do
We need to change seats
No need for that
Here I go
Uh..
Um.. I, I should be going now
Harry seems a bit gloomy
Harry
Huh?
Tongtong
So, do you feel great
with all the strength?
Harry found out that being strong
wasn't all that good
Will you change me back to
how I was?
How you were?
The spell was..
Kurikuri Tongtong
Kurikuri Tongtong.. Change!
Uh?
What is this?
That wasn't It.. Then..
Kurikuri Tongtong
Kurikuri Tongtong.. Change!
Huh? What..
Hmm.. Not this one either
Tongtong had to use his magic
until it became night time
What is this?
Pororo and friends
are fishing in the ocean
Huh?
Wow.. I got one
Wow.. It's big
Huh?
Uh?
Wow..
Oh..
Huh?
What a tiny fish
What?
At least I got a tiny fish
You didn't catch any..
What?
That's It! I'll show you!
Huh?
Pororo, what are you going to do..?
I'm going to catch a big fish!
What?
Whoa
Here
Crong
Crong Crong
I'll bet It's bigger than
the fish Eddy caught
Alright!
Tah tah
So, you don't think
I can do it too?
Yeap..
I'll catch a bigger one..
Alright!
Let's see who wins..
Oh no
There's a shark near by
A fish
You..!
Stop! I'll catch you
The shark is going after Pororo!
Umm.. A fish
Stop right there!
Uh.. Where did it go? Huh?
Wow.. It's big
Get you
Huh?
A.. sh, shark
Pororo is in danger
Huh?
That does It..
Er.. Pororo.. Run away!
Pororo, let's get out of here!
Almost there.. Huh?
Wait
Go back Or else you're
going to get it from me!
The friends have rescued
Pororo and Poby
I warned you
You guys
I caught a fish
Eddy!
Huh?
Watch out!
There's a shark!
Huh?
This time, Eddy is in danger
Save me!
Eddy, run!
Huh? Rody!
Huh?
Rody!
Are you alright?
Eddy..
Rody! Rody!
He's awake..
What a relief..
You saved Eddy
Thanks, Rody
it was nothing..
Thank goodness
everyone is alright
Shark.. That's what you get
for being mean to the others
Pororo and friends are
at Eddy's house
How is it?
Eddy made
another interesting toy
Wow.. It's wonderful..
Eddy, can I borrow this?
Just for a day, huh?
Hmmm..
Alright.. But don't break It..
Thanks
Crong
Crong Crong
Crong? Crong
So, you want it that way, huh?
Crong?
Crong!
Put that down!
You two..
if you're going to fight
I won't let you borrow It..
We, we won't fight
Crong Crong
So Pororo and Crong..
Borrowed Eddy's toy
and went back to home
Crong..
Crong Crong
Huh? Crong Crong?
Crong
Huh?
Crong Crong
This?
I'll move it from here
Crong
Crong Crong
Alright..
Crong Crong Crong
Crong Crong
That's it
Huh?
Crong Crong..
Crong?
Crong..
Alright!
Crong?
I turned it off
Crong! Crong Crong!
Catch it if you can
Pororo and Crong are
fighting over the toy
Catch it if you can..
Crong..
Crong?
Crong!
Crong
Crong! Crong!
Crong Crong Crong!
Crong! Croro!
Crong!
Oh dear, Crong went outside
Ohh..
I'm, I'm, I'm
the little singer
I love to sing..
Yes, I do.. Huh?
Ummm..
Poby!
Wh, What?
I'm singing for you
and you fall asleep?
i, I'm sorry
Crong..
Huh?
Crong
Why are you here alone so late?
Crong Crong..
Pororo wasn't having fun playing
with the toy without Crong
Crong.. Crong
Crong.. Crong!
Where did he go
when it's snowing so hard?
Pororo went running out
looking for Crong
Pororo.. Huh?
He's not home
Crong?
Crong..
Bye
Good bye
You guys
Pororo
have you seen Crong?
Crong?
Crong was worried about Pororo
Cororo
Pororo
Pororo!
Crong!
Huh?
Huh? It's Crong
Crong!
Cororo
Crong! Where were you?
Do you know
how much I was looking for you?
No matter how many times
they fight
Pororo and Crong
are the best of friends
The friends are gathered
at Loopy's house today
Loopy is baking delicious cookies
Wait a little longer and
the cookies will be done
What should we do
while we wait?
Crong Crong
How about telling tales?
Yes, I have one to tell
Long, long ago, in an ice land
there was a beautiful palace..
And in this palace
lived King Harry
a very beautiful princess Petty
and an even more
beautiful princess Loopy
What? Princess Loopy
is prettier than Princess Petty?
It's just an old tale
Humph!
It's time my princesses
got married..
Your Majesty
I would like to marry a prince
who brings me the most
interesting thing in the world
is that so?
Then you will marry the prince
who brings the most
interesting thing in the world
So, all the princes of
the other countries
started to bring
something interesting
First. Guest
Prince. Eddy. From. Fox. Land
What did you bring?
I have brought a one
and only robot
A robot?
What's so interesting about that?
Let me show you
Rody..
Um..
Do you call that interesting?
Rody
Yes!
Errr.. isn't it interesting?
Guards!
Take them away
Yes.. Pipipipipi..
Well, good bye then
Second.. Guest
Prince. Tongtong
From. Dragon. Land.
I have brought a magic crystal
that answers anything
Wow.. That's interesting
Crystal ball
who is the fairest in the world?
Snow white is the fairest
in the world
What?
W, wait a minute
I'll ask the question
Who is the fairest in the world?
The fairest is Snow.. oop!
Try asking something else?
That's OK! Humph!
You may go now
have the next guest come in
Third. Guest. is
Prince. Poby. From. Bear. Land
Wow.. A violin
This is a magic violin
Oh yes.. Oh?
Oh.. What is this?
Who ever hears this violin
is bound to dance
Oh.. Guards!
Take this man out
Yes.. Pipipipipi..
Let the next guest come in
Yes
Fifth. Guest. is
Prince. Crong. From
Dinosaur. Land
And what is that?
Huh?
Crong Crong
As Prince Crong opened the box..
Blocks fell out of it
and filled the palace
Oh! Guards!
Take that man out of here!
Crong?
Crong!
The. Last. Guest!
Prince. Pororo.
From. Penguin. Land.
Oh.. That's something
I've never seen before.. What is it?
It's a plane
You can fly anywhere in it
Then can I ride it?
Of course
Wow.. How exciting
I'm back, Your Majesty
How was it flying
in the sky, Princess?
it was very interesting..
Um..
You have brought the
most interesting thing in the world
Prince Pororo may
marry Princess Loopy
Um.. What? Wait!
Why?
But I want to marry
beautiful Princess Petty..
What? Humph!
Wow.. Cookies
Looks delicious
Wait!
Huh?
Answer my question
before you have any!
Who's the fairest?
Um.. Loopy
Pororo, and you?
Of course it's you, Loopy
Oh no
Petty is displeased with the answer
You are all wrong!
Huh?
The correct answer is
Loopy and Petty are the fairest
That's right
Loopy and Petty are both the fairest
The friends are going to
play soccer today
On Pororo's team
Pororo
Crong
Poby
Loopy
and Tongtong as the goal keeper
And on Eddy's team Eddy
Rody
Petty
Pipi
and Popo as the goal keeper
Play ball..
Crong.. Catch!
CrongCrong
Err.. I'm here to block
Crong!
Here it goes
Popo?
Goal!
CrongCrong
Pororo's team is winning 1 :0
I. Am. Sorry
That's alright
You'll do better next time
Eddy.. Catch
Alright! Here goes
I got him
Left!
Then right!
Left again.. Then, right!
Oh, I'm tired!
Give it to me
Okay, Rody
Here it goes
Get it
Kurikuri Tongtong
Appear pretty flower
Oh, that's pretty
Loopy, It's a present
Thanks
Here I come
Huh?
The ball that Rody kicked hit
the goal post and bounced back
Oh!
Huh?
Pororo's team is winning 2:0
Yeah!
Alright! Let's do this
Now we have to block
any ball that comes!
Okay
Let's continue to play ball
Huh?
Pipi flew up and blocked the ball
That way!
Huh?
This time Rody suddenly turned tall!
I got it
Huh?
Goal!
Eddy's team made a goal
and the score is 2:1
Nice job, Rody!
That was nothing
Let's go
Stop him!
The Shark started
watching the soccer game
Crong! Here!
Crong!
Popopopo!
Rody!
Wait!
I got it
That's mine..
Pipi!
Oh..
Eddy's team scored again
and the score is tied 2:2
Okay!
Alright! Here goes!
Pipipi!
Huh?
Pipi blocked Pororo's balls
very well
Pipi!
Pipipipipi!
Well done!
Oh..
Here I go!
Kurikuri Tongtong
Kurikuri Tongtong Change!
This time Tongtong got larger
Rody!
Okay
The ball is flying too far
Oh dear, the shark
got hit by the ball!
The friends had to finish
the soccer match
instead, the shark had a great time
playing with the ball
It's morning..
There's Popo and Pipi's spaceship
Popo is fixing the spaceship
Popo?
Are. You. Sure
You. Fixed. It. Right?
Um.. It. Will. Fly. Anyways
See? It's. Working
Pipipipi
Popo
Do. You. Want. To. Try. it?
Me? O.K!
You. Are. Sure. It. Is. Fixed?
I'm. Sure
O.K! Beep..
Oh?
You. Said. That. You. Fixed. It!
That. Is. Strange
Pipipipi!
Oh!
Po. Po. You!
Stop!
Popo Pipi
Huh?
Hi we're here
HelIo
Come. In
Wow
It's very interesting in here
Oh?
What kind of a tree is that?
It's. A. Tree. From. Space
Wait. A. Minute
Here
Wow
Now. Let. Me. Show
You. Someting. Else
When. The. Light. Is. Gone
The. Tree. Changes. Back
When. It. Is. Dark
The. Tree. Lets. Out. Light
Wow
Wow.. We're in space
CrongCrong
Popo and Pipi's home should be
there among those stars..
Don't you wanna go back?
Yes. I. Want. To. Go
Eddy!
Oops!
Wait.. I'll sing a song to
make you feel better
Song?
Barabarabarabarabam Barabara..
Harry
Huh?
Shhh!
Popo, Pipi
Let's try to fix your space ship
I'll help you
You will?
Umm..
Are you sure you can fix it?
Of course
I'm a very smart fox, you know
Um..
It's looks finished!
Really?
Yes
is this the control handle?
Pipipi
Let's go
The space ship is flying!
Wow
Shall we go on a test flight?
Huh? This isn't working!
The space ship fell
into a mountain
Oh.. Are you alright?
No!
What was the problem?
Alright! I'll try again!
Huh?
Eddy, are you done fixing it?
No.. It's not done yet
But Eddy didn't give up
By night time, Eddy was finished
fixing the space ship
Finished
Really?
Yes.. Let's go on a test flight
one more time
Why do I feel like
It's not going to work again..
Eddy! What's going on?
I don't know
This time the space ship
crashed in the snow
The. Space
Ship.. It's Broken
Popo, Pipi..
I'm so sorry
I really wanted
to fix your space ship..
It's. Alright
You. Were. Only. Trying
To. Help. Us. Thanks
But I didn't fix it
And. We. Get. To. Stay. Here. Longer
With. You. Nice. Friends
That's. Right
We'll all help you fix it next time
Thanks
Although the spaceship was broken
the stars above shined brightly
because of the friends' warm hearts
Today, Eddy is helping Popo
and Pipi fix the space ship
Umm.. Okay
Finished!
I fixed it
It's working
Pipi, try flying it
Huh? Oh. O.K.
Pi pipipi..
It's. Fl. Flying!
It's. Really. Flying
Wow
You did it, Eddy
Great job, Eddy
Popo, Pipi, Congratulation!
Thank. You
You can go back home now
Yes
Let's get off
You. Guys
We. Will. Be. Going. Back
To. Our. Planet
Yes
Crong?
There are friends waiting
for Popo and Pipi to come home
Crong Crong..
Good bye
Bye
We. Had. A. Great. Time
Thank. You
It's time to say good bye
to Popo and Pipi
Good. Bye. Friends
Popo, Pipi
Wait a minute
Pi?
Here. Home made cookies
You liked it
Thank. You. Loopy
Thank. You
Come and visit us
if you want to have some more
We. Will
Bye
Crong Crong
Bye!
Popo and Pipi's space ship..
Flew up to go outer space
Good bye, Popo
Good bye, Pipi
Pipi! Pipi!
Wow
The space ship flew to planet Pipo
They finially arrived
Popo?
Pipi?
Popo Pipipipipi..
Popo and Pipi finially
met their beloved friends
Popopo
Pipipipi
Popopo? Pi?
Try. it
Pipi?
Popopopo!
Pipi? Pipipi! Pipipi Piri Piri
Oh dear, they have eaten away
Loopy's cookies
Hope they're safe
Crong crong
Pororo and friends are
gathered at Loopy's house
Do you think Popo and Pipi
went back home safe?
They should have..
isn't it kind of boring?
Boring
Crong?
Crong Crong! Popo, Pipi Crong!
Huh?
Crong!
Oh.. That's..!
Popo and Pipi!
Wow..
Pipipipi.. Pipipipipi
Good to have you back
Thank. You. Pororo
Hey, guys!
Come. Out
Every. Body. come. Out
These are my friends
from planet Pipo
Hello
Oh that..
The cookies that you had were
all made by Loopy
Huh?
Popopopo Pipipipipipi..
Why? What's going on?
They. Said. Your. Cookies. Were
The. Best. They. Ever. Had
Really? Wait
Who wants to have some cookies?
Loopy's cookies are fantastic
it brought Popo and Pipi back
to see Pororo and friends..
And helped bring new friends
from planet Pipo
PaPaPamPa PaPaPaPamPa
PaPaPamPa Pa
Playful Pororo
troublemaking Crong
Strong Poby, and little Harry
are all good friends
Clever Eddy, trustful Rody
Timid Loopy, and cheerful Patty
are all good friends
With different faces
and personalities
We are all good friends
In spite of the quarrels
and the missunderstanding
Always helping, and understanding
We are all good friends